<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="34">
	<page id="4816304" title="DeadAir T Files" descr="names used in DeadAir Mods" voice="yes">
		<!-- 3323247 == deadair -->
		<!--48163x69 == 3323247 since there is a character limit -->
		<!--48163##-->
		<t id="100">Caldari State</t>
		<t id="101">The Caldari State is ruled by several mega-corporations. There is no central government to speak of - all territories within the State are owned and ruled by corporations. Duty and discipline are required traits in Caldari citizens, plus unquestioning loyalty to the corporation they live to serve. The corporations compete aggressively amongst themselves and with companies outside the State, resulting in a highly capitalistic society.</t>
		<t id="102">CAL</t>
		<t id="103">Caldari Capital Equipment Licence</t>
		<t id="104">Caldari Capital Ship Licence</t>
		<t id="105">Managing Partner of the State</t>
		<t id="106">Member of the State</t>
		<t id="107">Caldari General Use Equipment Licence</t>
		<t id="108">Caldari General Use Ship Licence</t>
		<t id="109">Caldari Military Equipment Licence</t>
		<t id="110">Caldari Military Ship Licence</t>
		<t id="111">Caldari Police Licence</t>
		<t id="112">Caldari Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
		<t id="113">Caldari Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
		<t id="114">Caldari Advanced Module Licence</t>
		<t id="115">Caldari Basic Module Licence</t>
		<t id="116">Caldari Intermediate Module Licence</t>
		<t id="117">Caldari Trade Offer Subscription</t>
		<t id="118">State</t>
		<t id="119">Caldari Ship Sale Contract</t>
		<t id="120">Perimeter</t>
		<t id="121">Niyabainen</t>
		<t id="122">Ikuchi</t>
		<t id="123">New Caldari</t>
		<t id="124">Jita</t>
		<t id="125">Hirtamon</t>
		<t id="126">Kisogo</t>
		<t id="127">xxx</t>
		<t id="128">xxx</t>
		<t id="129">xxx</t>
		<t id="130">Maila</t>
		<t id="131">xxx</t>
		<t id="132">xxx</t>
		<!-- Equipment -->
		<t id="200">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="201">HAM</t>
		<t id="202">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="203">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Heavy Assault {20105,1121}(Dumbfire Launcher)</t>
		<t id="204">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,3001}(XL) Oblivion Kinetic Doomsday</t>
		<t id="205">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="206">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Scourge(K) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="207">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Inferno(T) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="208">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Nova(E) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="209">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="210">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Scourge(K) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="211">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Inferno(T) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="212">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Nova(E) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="213">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Light Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="214">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Mjolnir(EM) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="215">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Scourge(K) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="216">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Inferno(T) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="217">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Nova(E) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="218">LAM</t>
		<t id="280">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) {20107,3021}(All-round Engine)</t>
		<t id="290">{20111,5031}(L) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="291">{20111,5021}(M) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="292">{20111,5011}(S) Light Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="298">Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="299">Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<!-- Turret Description -->
		<t id="300">A launcher intended for use on cruiser-class spacecraft. While assault launchers do not possess the sheer damage-dealing capability of regular heavy missile launchers, their blend of speed and attack power lends them application across a good range of tactical situations.</t>
		<t id="304">Using a targeting and tracking control system more advanced than any other in existence, this weapon launches and controls a storm of missile fire capable of neutralizing almost any target.</t>
		<t id="305">An EMP warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="306">A kinetic warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="307">A plasma warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="308">A nuclear warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="309">Favored by many for its average capacity and firing rate. Useful in both fast attack raids and longer battles.</t>
		<t id="310">An EMP warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="311">A kinetic warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="312">A plasma warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="313">A nuclear warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
	</page>
</language>