<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="33">
	<page id="4816304" title="DeadAir T Files" descr="names used in DeadAir Mods" voice="yes">
		<!-- 3323247 == deadair -->
		<!--48163x69 == 3323247 since there is a character limit -->
		<!--48163##-->
		<t id="100">L'État Caldari</t>
		<t id="101">Les Caldari sont dirigés par plusieurs méga-corporations. Il n'y a pas de gouvernement central à proprement parler - tous les territoires de l'État sont détenus et dirigés par des sociétés. Le devoir et la discipline sont des qualités requises chez les citoyens de Caldari, ainsi qu'une loyauté sans faille envers la société pour laquelle ils vivent. Les sociétés se livrent une concurrence agressive entre elles et avec les entreprises extérieures à l'État, ce qui donne lieu à une société hautement capitaliste.</t>
		<t id="102">CAL</t>
		<t id="103">Licence d'équipement Caldari</t>
		<t id="104">Licence de vaisseaux capitaux Caldari</t>
		<t id="105">Associé de l'État</t>
		<t id="106">Membre de l'État</t>
		<t id="107">Licence d'équipement à usage général Caldari</t>
		<t id="108">Licence de vaisseaux à usage général Caldari</t>
		<t id="109">Licence d'équipement militaire Caldari</t>
		<t id="110">Licence de vaisseaux militaire Caldari</t>
		<t id="111">Licence de police Caldari</t>
		<t id="112">Licence du module de construction de vaisseaux capitaux Caldari</t>
		<t id="113">Licence pour les modules auxiliaires de construction navale Caldari</t>
		<t id="114">Licence pour les modules avancés Caldari</t>
		<t id="115">Licence des modules de bases Caldari</t>
		<t id="116">Licence des modules intermédiaires Caldari</t>
		<t id="117">Abonnement à l'offre commerciale Caldari</t>
		<t id="118">État</t>
		<t id="119">Contrat de vente du navire Caldari</t>
		<t id="120">Perimeter</t>
		<t id="121">Niyabainen</t>
		<t id="122">Ikuchi</t>
		<t id="123">New Caldari</t>
		<t id="124">Jita</t>
		<t id="125">Hirtamon</t>
		<t id="126">Kisogo</t>
		<t id="127">xxx</t>
		<t id="128">xxx</t>
		<t id="129">xxx</t>
		<t id="130">Maila</t>
		<t id="131">xxx</t>
		<t id="132">xxx</t>
		<t id="199">Caldari</t>
		<!-- Equipment -->
		<t id="200">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="201">HAM</t>
		<t id="202">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Heavy Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="203">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Heavy Assault {20105,1121}(Dumbfire Launcher)</t>
		<t id="204">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,3001}(XL) Oblivion Kinetic Doomsday</t>
		<t id="205">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="206">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Scourge(K) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="207">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Inferno(T) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="208">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Nova(E) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="209">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="210">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Scourge(K) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="211">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Inferno(T) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="212">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Nova(E) Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="213">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Light Assault Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="214">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Mjolnir(EM) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="215">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Scourge(K) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="216">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Inferno(T) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="217">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Nova(E) Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="218">LAM</t>
		<t id="219">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="220">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Scourge(K) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="221">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Inferno(T) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="222">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) Nova(E) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="223">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Mjolnir(EM) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="224">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Scourge(K) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="225">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Inferno(T) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="226">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5021}(M) Nova(E) Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="227">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Mjolnir(EM) Light Missile</t>
		<t id="228">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Scourge(K) Light Missile</t>
		<t id="229">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Inferno(T) Light Missile</t>
		<t id="230">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5011}(S) Nova(E) Light Missile</t>
		<t id="280">{4816304,102}(CAL) {20111,5031}(L) {20107,3021}(All-round Engine)</t>
		<t id="290">{20111,5031}(L) Heavy Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="291">{20111,5021}(M) Heavy Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="292">{20111,5011}(S) Light Missile Launcher</t>
		<t id="296">Light Missile</t>
		<t id="297">Heavy Missile</t>
		<t id="298">Light Assault Missile</t>
		<t id="299">Heavy Assault Missile</t>
		<!-- Turret Description -->
		<t id="300">A launcher intended for use on cruiser-class spacecraft. While assault launchers do not possess the sheer damage-dealing capability of regular heavy missile launchers, their blend of speed and attack power lends them application across a good range of tactical situations.</t>
		<t id="304">Using a targeting and tracking control system more advanced than any other in existence, this weapon launches and controls a storm of missile fire capable of neutralizing almost any target.</t>
		<t id="305">(EM)An EMP warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="306">(K)A kinetic warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="307">(T)A plasma warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="308">(E)A nuclear warhead designed for use with heavy assault launchers. Heavy assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than heavy missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="309">Favored by many for its average capacity and firing rate. Useful in both fast attack raids and longer battles.</t>
		<t id="310">(EM)An EMP warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="311">(K)A kinetic warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="312">(T)A plasma warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="313">(E)A nuclear warhead designed for use with light assault launchers. Light assault missiles can be fired at a greater rate than light missiles, at the expense of effective range.</t>
		<t id="314">(EM)First introduced by the armaments lab of the Wiyrkomi Corporation, the Mjolnir heavy missile is a solid investment with a large payload and steady performance.</t>
		<t id="315">(K)The Scourge heavy missile is an old relic from the Caldari-Gallente War that is still in widespread use because of its low price and versatility.</t>
		<t id="316">(T)Originally designed as a 'finisher' - the killing blow to a crippled ship - the Inferno heavy missile has since gone through various technological upgrades. The latest version has a lighter payload than the original, but much improved guidance systems.</t>
		<t id="317">(E)The be-all and end-all of medium-sized missiles, the Nova heavy missile is a must for those who want a guaranteed kill no matter the cost.</t>
		<t id="318">(EM)An advanced missile with a volatile payload of magnetized plasma, the Mjolnir light missile is specifically engineered to take down shield systems.</t>
		<t id="319">(K)From its humble beginnings in tiny Minmatar design labs, the Scourge light missile has quickly established itself throughout the star cluster as a premier missile for light launchers.</t>
		<t id="320">(T)The explosion the Inferno light missile creates upon impact is stunning enough for any display of fireworks - just ten times more deadly.</t>
		<t id="321">(E)The Nova light missile is a tiny nuclear projectile based on a classic Minmatar design that has been in use since the early days of the Minmatar Resistance.</t>
		<!-- Stations -->
		<t id="1101">Caldari Defence Platform</t>
		<t id="1111">Caldari Trading Station</t>
		<t id="1121">Caldari Equipment Dock</t>
		<t id="1131">Caldari Shipyard</t>
		<t id="1141">Caldari Wharf</t>
	</page>
</language>